did you hear the sound
你听到声音了吗
In front is the sleepy Longyuan
前面就是困龙渊
We have to quickly unlock the seal of the Dragon God
我们要赶紧解开龙神封印
Otherwise, wait for Cangliu to come.
不然等沧流的人来了
it's hard to deal with
就很难应付了
good
好
go
走
didn't care at the time
当时没在意
I thought we were going to catch
心想我们要捉拿的
must be a man with a weapon
定是携带武器的人
They don't have swords
他们没有带刀剑
Just let them into town
就让他们进城了
Major General please forgive me
请少将军恕罪啊
still a step too late
还是晚了一步
soldier on duty
当值守城士兵
negligent military law Watching at kisskh.me
玩忽失职 军法处置
Major General is not dereliction of duty
少将军 并非属下玩忽失职
The subordinate found the two of them
属下一发现他们两个
It's the two people on the arrest warrant.
正是缉拿令上的两个人
take away the subordinates
带走 属下
Major General Major General
少将军 少将军
Major General
少将军
Is this punishment too severe?
这处罚是否太过严厉了
They let no one else
他们放过的不是别人
but the sea emperor
而是海皇
Bai Ying and Su G have already arrived here first
白璎和苏摹已经先到了这儿
They will definitely go directly to trapped Longyuan.
他们一定会直接去困龙渊的
So what do we do next
那我们接下来怎么办
You lead your troops to the Sleepy Dragon Abyss immediately
你带兵立刻前往困龙渊
Remember
切记
take a mountain road away from the river
要走远离河道的山路
Do not touch any water source
不能碰任何水源
Why
为什么
I have reason
我自有道理
how about you
那你呢
then come
随后就到
Major General
是 少将军
Everyone obeys
所有人听令
Immediately follow me to the trapped Longyuan to capture the Emperor of the Sea
立即随我前往困龙渊捉拿海皇
Yes Watching at kisskh.me
是
Why is the Major General staying here?
少将军为何留在此处
you stand here
你站在这儿
don't have to come
不必跟来
This is the Sleepy Dragon
这就是困龙渊
Back then, King Xingzun captured the Dragon God
当年星尊王擒获了龙神
cut a line in the ground
在大地上劈了一条线
Lock the Dragon God here
把龙神锁在了这里
I feel a surge of anger Watching at kisskh.me
我感受到了一股愤怒
the power of despair
绝望的力量
for thousands of years
几千年来
No one can cross the barrier of trapped Longyuan
都没有人能够渡过困龙渊的结界
I go down first
我先下去
you are waiting for me here
你在这儿等我
no good
不行 说好的
It was poisoned in the river
这是在河中下毒了
Su G lets you swim as fast as you can
苏摹 任你游得再快
Faster than this water
快不过这流水
This poison is so fast
这毒这般快
This poison is so ferocious
这毒如此凶猛
But you should be fine if you take the meds.
不过吃了解药就应该没事了
What's the matter with you, Major
少将军 你怎么了
Yunhuang strange poison ghost red Yan
云荒奇毒幽灵红藫
you just got poisoned
您刚才中毒了
I have an antidote
我有解药
Didn't I tell you not to come out alone?
不是说了不让你一个人出来吗
Why do you act on your own?
怎么又擅自行动
The subordinates are worried about the Major General
属下担心少将军
let's go
走吧
Yes
是
The suicide by drowning
切勿入水
There are ghost red yams in the water
水中有幽灵红藫
I'm going to have a look
有人 我去看看
no need
不必了
You will die immediately if you touch this water
沾了这水 你会立刻没命
go
走
Bai Ying
白璎
just came down
刚才下来
Those fogs make me hallucinate
那些雾让我产生了幻觉
Don't worry I'm here
别担心 有我在
strangeness
奇怪
Why can't I find where the sleepy dragon cable is?
怎么找不到困龙索在哪儿
Let's split up
我们分头去找吧
Bai Ying
白璎
Remember
记得
We have reached the boundary of Fuyu County
我们已经到了嵢峿郡地界
The front is heavily guarded
前面守卫森严
Let's go by water
我们改走水路
Should we wait any longer for the left to make them
我们要不要再等等左权使他们
Rest for a while
原地休整片刻
If Yanxi didn't come
若是炎汐没有赶来
we won't wait
我们就不等了
Blame that Zhongzhou girl
都怪那个中州姑娘
Not accustomed to water, but still dragging the left power
不习水性还偏拖着左权使
Otherwise how fast can we go by water?
要不然我们走水路多快
talkative
多嘴
Can't wait to get into the water
不等了 下水
Anyway, Yanxi knows the way
反正炎汐识得路
rightist
右权使
There are cracks on the sound beads from Xiao
潇传来的音珠上有裂痕
I don't know if there is any sound
不知还有没有声音
never
切勿
It's Xiao's voice
是潇的声音
It's a pity that I can only hear the word "don't"
可惜只能听到切勿二字
Mo Feixiao was discovered when he was in the sound transmission beads
莫非潇在传音珠的时候被发现了
damaged sound beads
破坏了音珠
there is a possibility
有这个可能
Are you going to remind us
莫不是要提醒我们
Do not go trapped in Longyuan
切勿去困龙渊
Isn't that young master dangerous?
那少主岂不是很危险
Then we go by water
那我们走水路
go
走
Yanxi we are all the way
炎汐 我们一路
Walk along the mark left by Ning Liang
沿着宁凉留下来的标记走
Why haven't you met them yet?
怎么还碰不到他们呀
will they be okay?
他们不会出事了吧
Will not
不会的
Let's hurry up
我们还是加快脚程吧
good
好
how's it going
怎么样了
better
好点了
Ning Liang
宁凉
Yanxi
炎汐
what happened
怎么回事
we are poisoned
我们中毒了
Cang Liu set a level here
沧流在这里设置了关卡
forcing us into the water
逼迫我们下水
Toxic in water
在水里投入剧毒
what poison is this?
这是什么毒啊
It's too cruel
也太残忍了吧
This should be the ghost red yan
这应该是幽灵红藫
Ghost Red Yan
幽灵红藫
What happens after being poisoned
那中毒之后会怎么样
The poison is in the water
此毒在水里
As long as a person enters the water and touches the poison line
只要人一旦入水触碰毒线
Immediately, the entire body will be petrified to death in pain.
就会立刻全身石化 痛苦致死
Now it seems
现在看来
The water in the entire Suiyu County is filled with this poison.
整个嵢峿郡的水里都是此毒了
Cangliu people are too cruel
沧流人也太残暴了吧
Is there a cure for this poison?
那此毒有药可解吗
There must be an antidote for those who are poisoned
下毒之人必有解药
then let's go
那我们走
What's wrong
怎么了
We have spies in Cangliu Barracks
我们在沧流军营有探子
Why am I not getting any messages
为什么我没有收到任何消息
I received Xiao's tone beads
我收到了潇的音珠
But the bead is broken
但是音珠被破坏了
Okay, I'll definitely get the antidote back.
好 我一定拿回解药
go
走
Be careful
小心
sit here
坐这儿
give
给
Why doesn't this fog go away?
为什么这个雾还散不去
Neptune
海皇
help us help
救救我们 救命啊
save us save us
救救我们 救救我们吧
save our sea emperor
救救我们 海皇
sea ​​emperor sea emperor
海皇 海皇
Neptune
海皇
King Kongsang has already killed the blue seaside
空桑王已经杀到碧落海边了
He said
他说
He said that Princess Yaran poisoned Queen Baiwei
他说雅燃公主毒害白薇王后
Said to step on Hiraizumi to avenge the queen first
说要踏平泉先为王后报仇
If you want to fight
若欲讨伐
How can you send troops without a name
怎会出兵无名
Are those just now illusions again?
刚才的那些又是幻象吗
why so real
为何如此真实
Su G
苏摹
Su G is that you?
苏摹 是你吗
Su G, have you found the sleepy Long Suo?
苏摹 你找到困龙索了吗
The fog here is really weird
这里的迷雾确实诡异
Find the sleepy dragon first.
先去找困龙索吧
Su G
苏摹
Did I just tap the light-shielding beads twice?
是不是刚才我敲了两下避光珠
you feel me
你感受到我了
So I found it
所以才找过来的
yeah let's go
是啊 走吧
You are not Su G
你不是苏摹
Who are you
你是谁
why are you pretending to be him
你为什么要假扮他
I am Su G
我就是苏摹
Without the blessing of the Dragon God
没有了龙神的庇佑
From now on, Izumi will obey from generation to generation
从此泉先便会世代顺从
You killed Quan Xian today
你今日杀泉先
another day
他日
Kongsang must be destroyed by others
空桑必定被他人所灭
When will this back and forth stop
如此往复 何时休止
what are you doing
你干什么
You are no longer the Ah Lang I know
你已经不是我认识的那个阿琅
I grew up with my childhood sweetheart
跟我青梅竹马长大的
The good astronomer Ah Lang
善良星算师阿琅
but became the King of Stars that I no longer know
而是变成了我不再认识的星尊王
The back soil ring
这个后土戒指
i give you back
我还给你
Queen of Houtu ring
后土戒指 王后所有
How can this day and earth be ours?
这天和地怎么会为我们所有
The Seven Seas are where the ancestors of Izumi lived.
七海是泉先世代所居之地
Yunhuang is the home of all living beings
云荒是芸芸众生的家园
how can it be your everything
怎么会是你的一切
You don't get obsessed anymore
你不要再执迷不悟了
let it go
放手吧
who are you
你究竟是谁
i am you
我就是你
Are you an illusion or what?
你到底是幻象还是什么
I am not an illusion
我不是幻象
I'm the one who came to end you
我是来了结你的人
Today I will take back everything that belongs to me
今日我便要拿回属于我的一切
Su G
苏摹
Bai Ying
白璎
Who would that person be?
那人到底会是谁啊
It turns out to be an illusion
竟然会幻形之术
Seems to be waiting for us here on purpose
看来是刻意在此等我们的
Could it be someone sent by the prey?
会是鸷者派来的人吗
Not sure yet
还不太确定
Anyway, this place is weird
总之这个地方甚是诡异
There will always be delusional illusions
总是会有迷惑人心的幻象
Just now I too was caught up in the illusion of the past
刚刚我也卷入了前尘的幻象之中
Phantom of the Past
前尘幻象
I saw seven thousand years ago
我看到了七千年前
King Xingzun and Queen Baiwei are trapped in Longyuan here
星尊王和白薇王后在这困龙渊
I also saw Queen Baiwei
我也看到了白薇王后
how to die
是如何死的
What kind of past in that fantasy
那幻象之中有怎样一段过往
Queen Baiwei she
白薇王后她
she was killed
她是被杀死的
But I haven't seen the result yet
但是我还没有看到结果
Maybe it's an illusion
或许这也是一种幻象吧
You said you saw Queen Baiwei
你说你看到了白薇王后
Does Queen Baiwei look like me?
那白薇王后跟我长得像吗
picture
像
No wonder when I was in the Mirror Tower
难怪之前在镜塔的时候
Prey, he will call me Avi
鸷者他会叫我阿薇
Not only that
不仅如此
True Lan and King Xingzun
真岚与星尊王
I look exactly the same as Chunhuang
我与纯煌都长得一模一样
It seems that this trapped Longyuan not only seals the Dragon God
看来这困龙渊不仅封印龙神
It also hides the secrets from 7,000 years ago
还隐藏着七千年之前的秘密
Then you say we look so much like them
那你说我们跟他们长得那么像
between us and them
我们与他们之间
Is there some mysterious connection?
会不会有什么神秘的连接啊
Bai Ying
白璎
you are you
你就是你
Even if two people look alike
即使两个人长得像
two completely different people
也是完全不同的两个人
have a different destiny
有着不同的命运
before knowing the truth
在不知道真相之前
Don't be fooled by the stuff here
不要被这里的东西所迷惑
what happened to you
你怎么了
Bai Ying is not safe here
白璎在这里不安全
If she really has anything to do with Bai Wei
如果她真的和白薇有什么关系
let's go
我们走
Although you and I are superiors
你我虽为上下级
But don't be so rigid
但不必如此拘泥
The poison of red yan is your masterpiece
红藫之毒可是你的杰作
nothing to do with her
与她无关
she's with you all day
她整日跟你在一起
I didn't get a chance to talk to her
我并没有机会跟她说话
you go out
你出去吧
Yes
是
Who told you that
谁告诉你的
There are many people who saw the corpse of the merman by the river
有许多人看到河边的鲛人尸体
petrified
已经浑身石化
That's what the merman in the camp said
那就是营中的鲛人说的
Feather magic
羽幻
young
年少时
I'm just living in Fuchu all day
我只不过是成日在府中
A young master who bullied the maid
欺负丫鬟的一个小少爷
a playboy
一个纨绔子弟
It's you who taught me hard and woke me up
是你狠狠教训我 打醒我
I just followed you into the Wakamatsu Hall
我才随你进入若松堂
to become a warrior
才成为沧流的战士
say the point
说重点
The point is
重点就是
You most disdain this small trick of poisoning
你最不屑于下毒这种宵小手段
why are you now
为何你现在变得
No longer like the Yuhuan I used to admire
不再像我以前敬佩的羽幻
just be yourself
做你自己就好
don't admire me
不用敬佩我
I haven't changed
我也没有变
you've changed
你变了
did you
你以前
When I saw Nan Zhao tortured and killed the merman
看到南昭虐杀鲛人的时候
you'll help like me
你会像我一样出手相助
You know the poison of red yan
你知道红藫之毒
How many innocent people will be killed?
会害死多少无辜的人吗
innocent
无辜
Fei Lian
飞廉
those people
那些人
is our enemy
是我们的敌人啊
That Su G has already got the Heaven-defying Sword
那个苏摹已经拿到了辟天剑
how
怎么
Are you waiting for him to summon the Dragon God?
你要等他把龙神召唤出来吗
Either you have to strategize with me
你要么跟我制定一下战术
if you don't want to
你若不想
Camp bar
巡营吧
I'm off to camp
我去巡营了
Why are there so many guards?
怎么这么多守卫啊
How are we going to get in in a while?
一会儿我们该怎么进去啊
I'll draw your attention
我帮你引开注意
you hide in
你隐身进去
It's you, you're Ting's sister
是你 你是汀的姐姐
you're all right
你没事
Yuhuan fell into the water, the ghost red Yan
羽幻在水里下了幽灵红藫
I have news for you
我传了消息给你们
Why are you still in the water
为何你们还要入水
Ning Liang received the sound beads
宁凉收到了音珠
But the sound beads are broken
但音珠被破坏了
We did not receive the complete message
我们没有收到完整的消息
No wonder
难怪
I was planning to entangle Fei Lian while he was drunk.
我本打算趁飞廉酒醉缠住他
message again
再传一次消息的
where is the antidote
那 那解药在哪儿
in the phantom
在羽幻那里
Feather magic
羽幻
Wouldn't it be more difficult
岂不是更难了
I have a way
我有办法
But I need you to cooperate with me
但需要你们配合我
any solution
什么办法
Somebody caught a spy
来人 抓到一个探子
how is he
怎么是他
Fly fast and come closer
快 飞廉再走近
I'm afraid you won't be able to run away
你恐怕就跑不掉了
Xiao
潇
How about it
怎么样
I still pushed Xiao into the water.
我还是把潇推下水了
She must have been poisoned by the ghost red Yan
她应该中了幽灵红藫之毒
Yuhuan is not easy to lie
羽幻不好骗
If you don't do it real
如果不做得真一点
If there are other witnesses
还有其他人证的话
Yuhuan won't believe it anymore
羽幻更不会相信了
But this time there is real evidence
但是这回是真的有人证了
Fei Lian seems to have seen me
飞廉好像看见我了
Fei Lian
飞廉
Are you sure he sees you
你确定他看清你了
have no idea
不知道
But I see him
但是我是看清他了
Will he think
他会不会以为
Xiao is with us
潇跟咱们是一伙的
Acting cheat antidote
演戏骗解药
It's over, it's over, it's over
完了完了 前功尽弃了
Xiao is also hurt in vain
潇也白白受伤了
don't worry
你别急
Even if Fei Lian really sees you
就算飞廉真的看清你了
He might not even be able to think of that.
他也未必能想到那一层
What's more, in the eyes of Cang Liu
更何况在沧流人眼里
Xiao is Quanxian's traitor
潇是泉先的叛徒
It makes sense for you to hurt her
你伤她也是在情理之中
Now we can only wait and see what happens
现在我们就只能静观其变
wait patiently
耐心等待了
Yu Huan, if you have an antidote, give it to Xiao quickly.
羽幻你要有解药赶紧给潇吧
What exactly is going on
这到底是怎么回事
i caught a spy
我抓到一个探子
I wanted to send her to the camp
本想把她送入营中
I didn't want to be pushed into the river by her.
却没想被她推入河里
let her escape
让她逃走了
See who the spy is?
看清那探子的身份了吗
I haven't had time to look closely
我还没来得及仔细看
she struggled
她就拼命挣扎
what about you?
你呢 看清了吗
I only vaguely see a woman
我只隐约看到是个女子
It must be the merman who came to explore the way.
应该是来探路的鲛人吧
shark
鲛人
a shark
一个鲛人
How can I run away under your nose?
怎么会在你们眼皮底下跑掉
The shark ran very fast
那鲛人跑得极快
And Xiao fell into the water
而且潇还掉入水中
i have to save her
我得去救她
except me
除了我
And many soldiers saw Xiao being pushed into the river
还有很多士兵看到潇被推入河中
come
来人
exist
在
any of you have seen
你们有谁曾看见
Xiao was pushed into the water by the spies
潇被探子推入水里了
Return to the Major General
回禀少将军
I saw with my own eyes
属下亲眼见到
Xiao caught a spy
潇抓住了一个探子
The spy pushed Xiao into the water
那个探子把潇推入水中
suddenly disappeared
又突然消失不见
The rest of the patrol team saw it too.
其他巡防小队的人也都看见了
be able to prove
能够证明
What does disappearing mean
消失不见 什么意思
That spy knows a little magic
是那探子会一点法术
So Xiaocai has no enemy
所以潇才没有敌过
being pushed into the water
被推入水中
go down
下去吧
Yes
是
don't you believe me
你难道连我的话都不信了
you have always been sympathetic to the enemy
你素来对敌人同情
You mean I colluded with Xiao
你的意思是我跟潇串通好
Is it the antidote to deceive the ghost red Yan?
来骗幽灵红藫的解药是吗
even so
即便是这样
I can't hurt Xiao like this.
我也不能把潇伤成这样啊
Major General is incompetent
少将军 是属下无能
Major generals don't have to waste antidote for their subordinates
少将军不必为了属下浪费解药
Xiao is willing to accept
潇甘愿承受
Xiao is your subordinate
潇是你的手下呀
Born to die with you
跟你出生入死
you can really watch
你真能眼睁睁地看着
Was she tortured to death by the poison of the ghost red Yan?
她被幽灵红藫之毒折磨至死吗
life and death
生死由命
Major General Fei Lian thank you
飞廉少将军 感谢您
But you don't have to plead for me
但您不必为我求情
give
给
Xiaofeilian said that I have changed
潇 飞廉说我变了
become stone-hearted
变得铁石心肠
Is that right
是这样吗
Major General has not changed
少将军未曾改变
But maybe you've changed
但或许是你们变了呢
Xiao has not changed
潇 也没变
I hope so
但愿如此吧
Come out
出来吧
go
走
Are you here to find the antidote?
你们是来找这解药的吧
how do you know
你怎么知道
I'm not stupid
我又不傻
I can see your face
我都看清了你的脸
Xiao insisted that no
潇却坚称说没有
So you are a gang
所以你们是一伙的
Xiao?
潇呢
she's badly hurt
她伤得不轻
But have taken the antidote
但已经服过解药
It should be fine
应该没有什么大碍了
You better go now
你们还是赶紧走吧
It will be troublesome if someone comes later
待会儿来人了可就麻烦了
What about you
那你怎么办
Yu Huan found that the medicine was running out
羽幻发现药少了
will definitely investigate
一定会调查的
I am the Major General of Cangliu
我是沧流的少将军
And the love that grew up with him
还有跟他一起长大的情分
He probably won't start with his friends, will he?
他应该不会对朋友下手的吧
That
那
Xiao?
潇呢
Don't worry I will protect her
放心 我会保护她
thank you
多谢
You leave here with me
你们撤 这里有我
you can stealth
你会隐身术 赶紧走
Fei Lian can't stand it
飞廉 对不住了
go fast
快走
Don't come, come again and I'll kill him
别过来 再过来我就杀了他
Put down the weapons
都把兵器放下
Fei Lian
飞廉
You say I have changed
你说我变了
Actually you have changed
其实是你变了
Yanxi Run
炎汐 跑
Feather magic
羽幻
long time no see you
好久没有跟你
Have a good fight
痛痛快快地打一场了
who wants to fight with you
谁要跟你痛快打
This is the sleepy dragon platform, right?
这里就是困龙台了吧
should be
应该是
your back
你的后背
This is the mark of the Dragon God
这个是龙神印记
Dragon God should be nearby
龙神应该就在附近
i can feel it
我能感觉到它
what happened to you
你怎么了
I feel
我感觉
I feel like there's a pair of eyes watching us
我感觉有一双眼睛在监视我们
Eye
眼睛
She seems to have a lot to say to me
她好像有很多话要跟我说
I can feel her presence
我能够感受到她的存在
who is she
她是谁
have no idea
不知道
no matter what happens
不管发生什么事情
you have to tell me in time
你都要及时告诉我
why can't i speak
为何我说不出话来
Body can't move
身体也动弹不得
Why can't my hand
为何我的手动不了
you finally woke up
你终于醒了
Why is Su G so strange?
苏摹怎么如此奇怪
It's like you don't know me
好像不认识我一样
No
不
This person is not Su G
这个人并不是苏摹
you do not need to worry
你不用担心
you're just frightened
你只是受到惊吓
not seriously injured
没有受很严重的伤
where is this
这是哪儿
This is the Longxiao Palace
这里是龙绡宫
where is my boat
我的船呢
And the people on the boat?
还有船上的人呢
Your ship should have sunk to the bottom of the ocean
你的船应该沉到海底了
i only see you
我只见到你
didn't see anyone else
没有看见其他人
you have a good rest
你先好好休息
I'll see you later
我晚点再来看你
don't think about it
别多想
correct
对了
thank you
谢谢你
What's your name
你叫什么名字
pure brilliance
纯煌
I am Bai Wei
我是白薇
Su G
苏摹
Did it just
难道刚才
It's the 7,000-year-old illusion you're talking about
就是你说的那个七千年前的幻象
you also saw
你也看到了
I seem to have gone back to seven thousand years ago
我好像也回到了七千年前
I can't speak
我没有办法说话
There's no way to move
也没有办法动弹
It seems that I am Queen Baiwei
好像我就是白薇王后
Me too
我也是
This phantom is really weird
这个幻象真的很奇怪
What did you see in the vision
你在幻象之中看到了什么
should be pure huang
应该是纯煌
When I first met Queen Baiwei
和白薇王后初相识的时候
in Longxiao Palace
在龙绡宫
right
对
We should have fallen into the same illusion at the same time
我们应该同时坠入了同一个幻象
To kill, to kill
要杀要剐 悉听尊便
neither kill you nor cut
不杀你 也不剐
Put Fei Lian in my tent
把飞廉押进我的营帐里
Don't let him out without my permission
没有我的允许 不准他出来
Major General
少将军
You know how to call me Major General
你还知道叫我少将军
Today's business is yours
今天的事情有你一份吧
don't say yes?
不说是吗
ok let me speak for you
好 我替你说
You take advantage of my last hope for you
你利用我对你最后的一点期许
Don't hesitate to jump into the poisonous river
不惜跳入有毒的河里
Let's work together with Fei Lian
再跟飞廉里应外合
The antidote for deceived my ghost red yan
欺骗了我幽灵红藫的解药
finally gave him
最后给了他
right
对吗
I gave you one last chance
我给过你最后一次机会
Let you choose between me and Su G
让你在我和苏摹之间选择一个
this is your answer
这就是你的答案
Fei Lian and Feather Magic
飞廉和羽幻
Maybe there is a heart of loyalty and retribution
或许有一颗忠君报效之心
Maybe I can help you
也或许对你我有相救之举
But in the end they are for
但他们终究为的是沧流
I'm just making the best use of you
对你我不过是尽其利用
Who would you choose between us?
我们之间你到底选谁
say
说话
Say
说
Master Su G
苏摹少主
Xiao
潇
I didn't think about it
我不是没想过
The sharpest weapon around me can hurt me
我身边最犀利的武器会伤到我
But I still leave you
但我还是留下了你
now
现在
you're useless to me
你对我没有一点作用了
Xiao
潇
I will let your leftist
我会让你们的左权使
take your place
接替你的位置
throw her in the river
把她扔到河里
Ning Liang
宁凉
Nasheng
那笙
Have you got the antidote, Yanxi?
解药拿到了吗 炎汐呢
Yan Xi Yan Xi
炎汐 炎汐
Yanxi and I sneaked to the camp
我和炎汐偷偷溜到了驻扎营地
Xiao help us get the antidote
潇帮我们拿到了解药
However, in order to draw away the officers and soldiers, Yan Xi
但是炎汐为了引开官兵
He was captured by Yu Huan
他被羽幻抓走了
Yan Xi was captured
炎汐被抓走了
He said he said let me come back first
他说 他说让我先回来
Said that the poison of ghost red Yan can't wait
说幽灵红藫的毒等不了
This is the antidote
这个是解药
There aren't many in there
里面没有几颗了
Put these medicines in the water
把这些药化到水里
drink for the soldiers
给战士们喝了
Yes
是
we are late
是我们来晚了
Don't blame yourself, you've done your best
不必自责 你已经尽力了
Yanxi
炎汐
Yanxi is afraid that the bad luck will be less.
炎汐怕是凶多吉少了吧
Everyone has his mission
每个人都有他的使命
We also have our own mission
我们也有我们自己的使命
Ning Liang, you are right
宁凉 你说得对
No time to be sad now
现在没有时间难过
I want to use the power of this emperor
我要借助这皇天的力量
I want to save the dragon god
我要把龙神救出来
After Su G released the Dragon God
苏摹把龙神放了之后
Yanxi will be saved
炎汐一定会得救的
Nasheng
那笙
There are people all over the place
这儿到处都是沧流人
you are going to die
你这是去送死
Ning Liang, just let me go
宁凉 你就让我去吧
Yanxi Yanxi said this is his wish
炎汐 炎汐说这是他的愿望
Even if he doesn't come back
就算他以后不回来了
I want to help him make this wish come true
我也要帮他实现这个愿望
if you must go
一定要去的话
I'll send a few people to escort you
我派几个人护送你
Thank you, Ning Liang
谢谢你啊 宁凉
It's quiet here
这里寂静得
Makes you feel a little weird
让人感到有一丝的诡异
I can't seem to feel the presence of any living thing
好像感觉不到任何活物的存在
i can feel
我能感受到
There is a strong mind
这里有一股强大的念力
We should be stuck here
我们应该是被困在这里了
Those eyes appeared again
那双眼睛又出现了